Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/jay-mairsbab7388b (LinkedIn) www.skjm.com (Company)

Top Skills

Software Development

Java

C++

Certifications

Data Engineering on Google Cloud Platform Specialization

Deep Learning Specialization

Jay Mairs

Data Scientist at SUSTANY CAPITAL

Orange County, California Area

Summary

Experienced software developer with a demonstrated history of working in the computer software industry. Skilled in Data Science, Python, Deep Learning, Mobile App Development, Java, and C++. Strong entrepreneurship professional with a Master's Degree in Physics from University of California, Los Angeles.

Experience

SUSTANY CAPITAL

Data Scientist March 2018 - Present (2 years 1 month) Orange County, California Area

"The future is already here —

it's just not very evenly distributed."

This quote from futurist William Gibson has never been more pertinent than today. Sustany Capital invests in distributed, decentralized and disruptive technologies with long term viability.

SKJM, LLC Co Founder July 2008 - Present (11 years 9 months)

Peer Media Technologies VP Research & Development 2002 - 2008 (6 years)

OnSystems Inc. VP Research 1999 - 2002 (3 years)

Raytheon Software Developer 1998 - 1999 (1 year) IBM IT Specialist 1997 - 1998 (1 year)

Education

University of California, Los Angeles Master of Science (MS), Physics

Udacity
Nanodegree, Artificial Intelligence

University of California, San Diego Bachelor of Science (BS), Physics

University of California, San Diego Bachelor's Degree, Applied Mathematics

University of California, San Diego Bachelor's Degree, Psychology